Hi guys, how are you?
In the previous video, you watched Venilton,
D.I.O. expert, author of this course.
Now you will have a slightly different experience,
but still created by him.
The voice you are hearing was borrowed by Venilton himself
through an advanced technique of voice cloning.
About my appearance, it is obvious that I am not a representation of Venilton,
but I was carefully designed by him to co-create content.
Our goal with this is to provide a unique educational experience,
showing the potential of generative IAs like me in the teaching and learning process.
You may be wondering, but after all, what are generative IAs?
This is an excellent question.
Generative IAs are systems capable of creating, adapting and improving content
autonomously, always learning and improving.
Think of a mechanism capable of generating images, music, texts, voices,
and even virtual avatars, like what you see now.
All this with a quality that is similar to human work.
In the universe of generative IAs, we have stars like the GPT model,
the Generative Pre-trained Transformer,
which symbolizes a true revolution in artificial intelligence.
It stands out, especially when it comes to natural language processing,
understanding, generating and translating texts with incredible precision.
It is thanks to the GPT that we were able to transcribe and legendize this course
in three languages, Portuguese, English and Spanish.
Thus, we are expanding our accessibility with concrete steps
towards a more inclusive education on our platform.
Now that we know a little more about artificial intelligences,
it is worth noting how they are revolutionizing different sectors.
From the creation of digital art to the driving of autonomous vehicles,
these IAs are impacting various areas and, of course, education.
Here at DIO, we are exploring these technologies to offer a more dynamic,
immersive and especially accessible learning.
The world of generative IAs is wide and full of opportunities.
We are still in the initial stages for the discovery of all its potential.
So we invite everyone to join us on this fascinating journey,
in which we will explore some of the main practical applications of IAs today.
Are you ready? Let's go on this adventure together!